Menu

    * Village
* Travel

Last Updated: 17/10/2024

Privacy Policy
==============

[Tane Harre](https://tane.harre.nz/authors/tane/ "Tane Harre") 12/10/2018

**You have the right to ask for a copy of any personal information we hold about you, and to ask for it to be corrected if you think it is wrong. If you’d like to ask for a copy of your information, or to have it corrected or deleted, please contact us at privacy@harre.nz.**

This privacy policy (“Policy”) describes how Tane Harre processes your personal data. It applies to website visitors, job applicants and clients.

### 1\. Data Controller

The data controller responsible for collecting and processing your personal data is:  
  
Tane Harre  
Contact us at privacy@harre.nz.

### 2\. Processing Activities: Purpose, types of data collected, legal basis and storage.

We collect different categories of information based on the type of person and nature and purpose of the data processing. The below table describes how, why and for how long we process your personal data, depending on whether you are a website visitor, job applicant, or client.

| Person: | Purpose: | Data collected: | Legal basis: | Duration of Storage: |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| **Website Visitors** | **Using our website:**  <br>  <br>We automatically collect personal data from you through your web browser or device and through cookies.  <br>  <br>This collection is done:  <br>– to deliver the website,  <br>– optimize your experience,  <br>– obtain statistics. | IP-address, device type, browser type, referring site, pages accessed during your visit, cookies, the date, and time of each visit. | GDPR, Article 6(1)(a) (consent).  <br>GDPR, Article 6(1)(f) (our legitimate interest in providing the website, to improve user experience, and develop and improve our website). | Data relating to statistics and audience measurement are kept for up to 12 months from the date of your visit. (Specific storage periods depend on the individual cookie.) |
|     | **Website Communications:**  <br>We collect personal data directly from you to communicate with you and to respond to your queries. | Name and email address. | GDPR, Article 6(1)(f) (our legitimate interest in being able to respond to your enquiry and communicate with you). | Up to two years from the date on which you contacted us. |

In addition, this website uses You Tube to serve videos. You can read their Privacy Policy [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy#europeanrequirements).

This website also uses Google search to give search results if you use the sites search function. You can read their Privacy Policy [here](https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en-US#europeanrequirements).

### 3\. Recipients of personal data

Depending on the circumstances, we may share your data with:

* Service Providers, as part of our business operations and to perform certain services and functions, such as payment processing, marketing, web analytics, hosting, email communication and customer support services. Pursuant to our instructions, and to provide services to us, these service providers may access, process, or store your personal data.
* Public Authorities, if required to (i) comply with a legal obligation or lawful request by public authorities, (ii) protect and defend our legal rights or property, or (iii) protect against legal liability.

### 4\. Transfer of personal data to third countries

In certain situations, we will transfer personal data outside EU/EEA. Transfers to third countries are made on the following legal basis:

* the country has been deemed by the European Commission as having an adequate level of protection with respect to personal data; or 
* where the country does not have an adequacy decision from the European Commission, the Commission’s standard contractual clauses (“SCCs”) for the transfer of personal data to third countries will be put in place. To obtain a copy of our SCCs contact us at privacy@harre.nz.

### 5\. Your rights

When we process your data, you have the following rights:

* to access, rectify, or erase your personal data.
* to object to or restrict the processing of your personal data.
* if the processing of your personal data is based on your consent, to withdraw your consent at any time.
* to receive a copy of your personal data in a structured, commonly used, and machine-readable format (data portability).
* to determine the retention, deletion, and communication of your personal data after your death.
* to file a complaint with a supervisory authority (in France, the Commission nationale de l’informatique et des libertés (CNIL)).

You can exercise your rights by contacting us; see Section 6.

### 6\. Contact Tane Harre regarding your privacy

If you have questions about our processing of your personal data, or if you wish to exercise your rights, please contact us at privacy@harre.nz. We will respond to your request within one month. If your request is not sufficiently precise or does not contain all the elements required to answer your request, we may ask you to provide additional details.

You may also file a complaint with your local data protection authority. In France, this authority is:

Commission nationale de l’informatique et des libertés (CNIL)  
3 place de Fontenoy  
TSA 80715  
75334 PARIS CEDEX 07  
Telephone: +33 (0)1 53 73 22 22  
If you wish to file a complaint with the CNIL, you can complete the online form available at: www.cnil.fr/fr/plaintes  
Website: https://www.cnil.fr

### 7\. Amendments to our privacy policy

We will take all reasonable steps to communicate any changes to this Policy and will post any updated Policy on our website.

Updated: 3 October 2023.

This article was updated on 11/10/2023

#### [Tane Harre](https://tane.harre.nz/authors/tane/ "Tane Harre")

I am a New Zealander, living in France, who is interested in guitar, hiking, opensource, privacy, science and the general malaise of society.

### Related posts

#### [GDPR Privacy Policy Overview for New Zealand](https://tane.harre.nz/gdpr-privacy-policy-overview-for-new-zealand/)

24/05/2018

#### [Data privacy allows for freedom of thought and speech](https://tane.harre.nz/data-privacy-allows-for-freedom-of-thought-and-speech/)

07/05/2018

#### [What is the cost of privacy online?](https://tane.harre.nz/what-is-the-cost-of-privacy-online/)

12/05/2018

Comments
--------

### Featured

    [Useful Applications on Linux](https://tane.harre.nz/useful-applications-on-linux/) 09/10/2023

    [Walking the Pyrenees](https://tane.harre.nz/walking-the-pyrenees/) 31/10/2019

    [Robert Louis Stevenson Trail - GR70](https://tane.harre.nz/robert-louis-stevenson-trail-gr70/) 02/07/2019

    [Te Araroa - The long pathway](https://tane.harre.nz/te-araroa-the-long-pathway/) 08/06/2018

### Tags

* [Apache](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/apache/) (1)
* [Appenzell](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/appenzell/) (6)
* [Avon](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/avon/) (1)
* [Barbizon](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/barbizon/) (3)
* [Bois le Roi](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/bois-le-roi/) (1)
* [Bourron Marlotte](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/bourron-marlotte/) (5)
* [Coromandel](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/coromandel/) (6)
* [COVID-19](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/covid-19/) (10)
* [Dammarie-les-Lys](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/dammarie-les-lys/) (1)
* [Debian](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/debian-11/) (5)
* [Education](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/education/) (2)
* [Email](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/email/) (2)
* [Facebook](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/facebook/) (1)
* [File Sharing](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/file-sharing/) (3)
* [Fontainebleau](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/fontainebleau/) (17)
* [Fontainebleau Info](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/fontainebleau-info/) (49)
* [Food](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/food/) (3)
* [France](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/france/) (40)
* [Great Barrier Island](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/great-barrier-island/) (12)
* [Grez Sur Loing](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/grez-sur-loing/) (4)
* [Internet Party](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/internet-party/) (39)
* [KDE](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/kde/) (1)
* [Larchant](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/larchant/) (2)
* [Linux](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/linux/) (16)
* [Linux Mint](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/linux-mint/) (4)
* [LMDE6](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/lmde6/) (1)
* [Nemours](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/nemours/) (1)
* [New Zealand](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/new-zealand/) (34)
* [Nextcloud](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/nextcloud/) (1)
* [Noisy-sur-École](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/noisy-sur-ecole/) (1)
* [OMV6](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/omv6/) (1)
* [Playgrounds](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/playgrounds/) (14)
* [Politics](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/politics/) (46)
* [Printers](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/printers/) (1)
* [Privacy](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/privacy/) (19)
* [Pyrenees](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/pyreneese/) (16)
* [Recloses](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/recloses/) (1)
* [Review](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/review/) (8)
* [Robert Louis Stevenson Trail](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/robert-louis-stevenson-trail/) (13)
* [Saint Mammes](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/saint-mammes/) (1)
* [Saint Pierre lès Nemours](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/saint-pierre-les-nemours/) (1)
* [Switzerland](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/switzerland/) (6)
* [Te Araroa](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/te-araroa/) (108)
* [Te Henga](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/te-henga/) (1)
* [Thomery](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/thomery/) (1)
* [Thoughts](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/thoughts/) (30)
* [Travel](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/travel/) (2)
* [Ury](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/ury/) (1)
* [Villiers en Biere](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/villiers-en-biere/) (1)
* [Villiers sous Grez](https://tane.harre.nz/tags/villiers-sous-grez/) (1)

© [Blue Fountain](https://bluefountain.eu/) | [Disclaimer](https://tane.harre.nz/disclaimer/) | [Privacy Policy](https://bluefountain.eu/privacy-policy.html)
